Privacy policy
==============

* Privacy Policy

**Our Privacy Policy (“Privacy”) is designed to explain what information we collect from you as a user, how your information is collected, and how we may use it on our website everhour.com, and other websites and services that we operate.**

As you will see in the Policy, we only use the information collected to improve our services for our users. If after reviewing the Policy you have any further questions, please contact us at ask@everhour.com.

Information privacy
-------------------

Everhour maintains reasonable security measures to protect your information from loss, destruction, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure. This helps to ensure that your data is safe, secure, and only available to you and those you provide with authorized access.

We will share your personal information with third parties ONLY in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not and will not sell your personal information to third parties.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure due to the nature of the distributed network that is the Internet. Everhour is not liable for any loss or damage resulting from data gathered by unauthorized access to our sServices from hacking, social engineering, or otherwise circumventing our security measures. We do, however, take appropriate measures to try to prevent such events from occurring.

Your personal information
-------------------------

We collect the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email. When you browse our marketing pages, we track that for analytical purposes (conversion rates and testing new designs). We'll also store any information you voluntarily submit (for example, filling out a survey) for the duration of the research project or as long as it makes sense.

When you sign up for Everhour, we ask for your name, email address, country and company name. This allows us to personalize your new account, and send you invoices, updates, or contact you concerning your account. We’ll never give nor sell your personal information to third parties.

How we use your information
---------------------------

* To create your account;
* To bill you for services;
* To provide customer support;
* To transfer your information in the case of a sale, merger, consolidation, or acquisition;
* To better understand your needs and interests;
* To send newsletters;
* To personalize your experience;
* To improve our Services;
* To send you updates and alerts and to contact you about your account;

How we share and disclosure your personal information
-----------------------------------------------------

While we never share your personal information with non-affiliated companies, we may share your personal information in the following ways:

* We may share information with service providers who provide necessary services to Everhour (our Suprocessors) – for instance to send out newsletters or to process payments;
* When we have your permission to share your information;
* When we are required by law, or legal process to disclose that information – such as a valid court order or a valid subpoena. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a valid governmental request.
* To enforce our terms or to protect our operations or users;
* If a transfer of your information is required under the terms of a reorganization, merger, or sale of the company;
* When we determine that information is aggregate information or other information that does not identify you;

Cookies
-------

When you use the Everhour Service we and our Subprocessors may use “cookies”, “web beacons”, and similar devices to track your activities. These small pieces of information are stored on your hard drive, not on the Everhour website.

We use cookies to help you navigate the Everhour website and Service as easily as possible, and to remember information about your current session. We do not use this technology to spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy. You can disable cookies and tracking technologies through your web browser, however doing so may render the Everhour Service unusable.

Analytics
---------

We use Google Analytics to measure and evaluate access to and traffic on our Services. Google operates independently from us and has its own privacy policy, which we strongly suggest you review.

Security and storage
--------------------

The Everhour website and Service has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your information.

All data is encrypted via SSL/TLS when transmitted from our servers to your browser. These database backups are also encrypted. Data isn’t encrypted while it’s live in our database (since it needs to be ready to send to you when you need it), but we go to great lengths to secure your data at rest.

Correcting and updating information
-----------------------------------

If you are our customer and would like to access or delete information that you provided, you may do so by signing in to Everhour and making any changes required or by emailing us at ask@everhour.com. We will respond to your request within 14 days. We may decline to process unreasonable requests or requests that are not otherwise required by local law.

We retain your information and data that we process on your behalf as long as your account is active, as needed to provide our Services, and as necessary to comply with our legal obligations and to resolve disputes.

We have no direct relationship with third parties with whom our users may interact using the Services. Any such party who would like to amend or delete data which may be stored in the Services should direct his or her request to the applicable Everhour user acting as the “data controller” for such information.

Any such party who no longer wishes to be contacted by an Everhour user, should contact that Everhour user directly.

Deleted data
------------

When you remove your account, we delete all data associated with your account from our production database.

We do keep backups, designed for catastrophic system recovery, for 30 days. The backups are purged on a rolling 30 day cycle. When an account is deleted, none of your personal data will remain on our servers past 30 days. Anything you delete from your account while it’s active will also be purged from the backups on day 30.

Deactivated users will no longer have access to your account, but their name, email addresses, and time entries will remain in your account for historical reporting purposes.

Updates to this privacy
-----------------------

Everhour reserves the right to update this policy at any time without prior notice, so please review it frequently. Any significant changes to this policy will be sent out to the registered email address of the account owners.

Questions
---------

If you have any questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy, please email us at ask@everhour.com
